[ PANTING ]
[ MOANS ]
Oh , baby .
Tommy .
[ MOANING ]
Mmm . That was great , baby .
[ GROANS ]
Jody .
- Hi , Reg . - How 's it goin ' ?
Tommy 's gone .
It 's , uh ... it 's a hell of a way to end a trio .
It 's hard to believe ... he killed himself .
Yeah , I , uh ... I 'm gonna go visit somebody . I 'll catch ya inside .
Yeah .
[ GROWLING ]
[ MOTOR RUNNING ]
[ ENGINE DIES ]
[ ENGINE REVS , DIES ]
[ GROWLING ]
The funeral is about to begin ... sir .
Okay .
Sir .
[ ORGAN ]
REGGIE : It was a good idea not to let your little brother come to the funeral
and see Tommy like this .
JODY : Yeah , after Mom and Dad 's funeral , he had nightmares for weeks .
And forgive us our debts as we forgive our debtors .
Lead us not into temptation , but deliver us from evil .
Hey , I don 't like this place .
REGGIE : Well , say goodbye to Tommy .
JODY : Let 's just get the hell out of here .
- Hi , Michael . - Hi . Uh ... is your grandmother home ?
Sure . Come in .
Grandmother . Michael has returned and wishes to speak with you .
Grandmother is pleased you 've come and wants to know what 's bothering you .
Uh , tell her that I , um ...
She can hear you .
Oh , yeah .
Uh , it 's Jody again .
I found out that he 's leaving .
[ WHISTLING ]
I think it 's one of these headers in here .
[ CAR APPROACHING ]
Hey , Toby ! Hey .
- So what brings you back ? - Tommy .
Yeah , yeah .
Well , I just don 't get off on funerals , man . They give me the creeps .
I just wanted to tell you I heard about your folks . I 'm really sorry .
Yeah , thank you , man . That 's , uh ...
In two years I guess you can just about get over anything .
- So I hear you 've been out on the road . - Yeah .
How come you 're hanging around this dump ?
Well , I 'm taking care of the kid , you know .
Shit , I think after , uh , all that action , this town would drive you nuts .
You 're damn right . Hell , the kid 's 13 now .
Yeah , I 'm thinking of sending him off to live with his aunt .
But I 'll tell you , he sure ain 't gonna like it .
I mean , as it is , he follows me everywhere . It 's like he knows I 'm gonna leave .
He 's a tough little kid . I love him .
I 'm gonna miss him .
Grandmother has told you before not to worry .
If he does leave , he 'll take you with him .
- God , I hope she 's right . - She always is .
Uh , there 's something else .
I 'm really scared about something that I did .
I was messing around up at Morningside Cemetery , and I saw something .
Something really scary .
[ ENGINE SPUTTERS ]
Michael , grandmother wants to play a little game .
Wow ! How 'd you do that ?
Put your hand in the box .
- Well , what 's in it ? - Just put your hand in the black box .
Okay , but what 's in it ?
[ CLANGING ]
Hey , this thing really hurts !
Don 't fear , Michael .
- I can 't get my hand out . - Don 't fear .
- Give me back my hand ! - Don 't fear !
It was simply reflection . Fear is the killer .
That 's what grandmother wants you to learn .
Boy , that really hurt .
It was all in your mind .
Oh , yeah .
Come and visit us again soon .
Yeah .
[ LAUGHS ]
[ HUMMING ]
- Hiya , Reg . - Writing a new tune ?
Yeah , working on it .
# I 'm just a-sittin ' here at midnight #
# And I 'll be sitting here ' til noon #
# You see , my lady left me lonely #
# Yes , she did #
# My baby left me blue #
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
[ LAUGHING ]
All right . We 're hot as love , you know .
[ TUNING FORK TONE ]
[ TONE STOPS ]
[ LOUD TONE ]
[ TONE GROWS LOUDER ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Well , let 's see .
This is , uh ... just right up the street .
[ DOG BARKING ]
This is , uh ...
- kinda spooky , isn 't it ? - No , it 's exciting .
So , uh ...
what 's the only thing to do in this town ?
Well , it 's something ...
[ MOANS ]
Wow .
[ GROWLING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ YELLING ]
- What the heck ? - [ YELLING ]
Wait here . It 's my little brother .
I think he 's got some kind of a problem .
[ YELLING ]
Mike !
What 's wrong with you , man ?
There 's something up there . I know it . I saw it !
What ?
Okay , look , I was following you guys .
I didn 't mean any harm , but it 's out there and it 's gonna get me !
- What 's out there ? - I don 't know .
It was little and brown and low to the ground .
It was probably just a gopher in heat .
It wasn 't any gopher !
Where 's that girl , anyway ?
Well , she 's waiting back there for me , you idiot .
[ GROWLING ]
Did you hear that ?
Eh , it 's only the wind .
You better go get her before it gets her .
You got some kind of an overactive imagination or something , man ?
Look , tell you what .
You go on home . I 'll talk to you when I get back .
- You sure you 're gonna be okay ? - Ah , get out of here .
[ GROWLING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SNIFFS ]
Did that chick that I left with last night ever come back in here ?
What happened ? You get a hold of something you couldn 't handle ?
Nah , she just ditched out on me , I guess .
We were ...
messing around out there at Morningside .
- The funeral parlor ? - Yeah . Cemetery .
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GROWLING ]
Jody ? Is that you ?
[ RATTLING ]
[ SCREECH ]
[ GROANING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
You hit my fucking foot , man .
Oh , damn . I know you 're not gonna believe this , but these things were here .
Right in the garage and they were gonna get me .
Ah , gimme a break , will ya ?
They were jumping on the car and making these weird sounds .
Sure it wasn 't that retarded kid , Timmy , up the street ?
No , it was the same thing that chased me last night .
Well , what are we gonna do ?
You 're crazy , man .
[ GATE RATTLING ]
[ DOOR BANGS ]
[ BANGING NOISE ]
[ BANGING , RATTLING ]
[ WHIRRING NOISE ]
[ PANTING ]
[ GAGGING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
Um ...
Oh , shit .
[ LOUD RUSTLING NOISE ]
[ TAPPING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMING STOPS ]
[ POUNDING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
I 've gotta talk to you .
And it 's in that box ?
Yep .
Okay . I believe you .
Jesus !
What 's goin ' on up there ?
Well , there 's something I didn 't tell ya .
I was spying ' on Tommy 's funeral from the Groves with your binoculars .
And after everybody had left ,
that Tall Man picked up Tommy 's coffin all by himself
and put it in the hearse and drove off .
You 're crazy ! I helped carry that sucker myself .
It must 've weighed over 500 pounds .
[ SIGHS ]
I can 't figure this thing out .
But I do know one thing . Something weird is going on up there .
We 're goin ' for the sheriff . Go get your evidence .
All right !
That 's funny .
[ SCREECHING ]
[ CLICKING NOISE ]
[ BUZZING NOISE ]
Jody ! Jody !
JODY : What the ...
The garbage disposal .
- Come on . - [ BUZZING ]
Ready ? Go !
[ DISPOSAL MOTOR WHIRRING ]
[ WHIRRING STOPS ]
Would you look at that ?
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
Hey , guys .
I thought I 'd come over and see what was goin ' on
before the kids got out of summer school .
Mike , you wanna ride along with me today ?
It 's pretty warm outside and the ice cream 's gonna be flying fast and furious .
Remember how good you were at crowd control last time ?
Hey , what 's goin ' on here ?
- [ LOUD BUZZING ] - [ SCREAMS ]
[ DISPOSAL WHIRRING ]
[ WHIRRING STOPS ]
What the hell is goin ' on ?
Here , you keep that .
Now remember , you don 't aim a gun at a man unless you intend to shoot him .
And you don 't shoot a man unless you intend to kill him .
No warning shots .
- Hey , you listening to me ? - Yeah .
No warning shots . Warning shots are bullshit .
You shoot to kill or you don 't shoot at all .
Now you 'll be safe here . Lock all the doors and windows .
- And don 't follow me . - You sure you 're gonna be okay with that ?
I 'm just gonna go up there and take a look around . Nobody 's gonna see me .
But , heck , a Colt Army issue will put a man down and keep him there .
Remember that broken basement window around by the side .
And be careful .
- [ GROWLING ] - [ GRUNTS ]
- [ GRUNTING , GROANING ] - [ GROWLING ]
[ BITING ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ PANTING ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ PANTING ]
All right , who 's in there ?
Mike ?
Damn door latch . Get in .
Oh , here it comes !
There 's nobody driving ' that mother !
The pump 's in the backseat .
Okay . Slow down , and let him ride right up on our ass .
There was nobody ... there was nobody driving !
I 'm gonna get that bastard .
Oh , Jesus .
All right , speed up . I want to put a few in the engine .
Okay .
Holy shit !
[ WHOOPING ]
JODY : It 's one of those dwarves .
It went right through it .
Tommy !
Reggie .
We got one of ' em .
Uh , on Colton in the Groves .
All right . Uh , Reg ?
Bring your truck .
Holy Jesus ! You didn 't tell me the dwarf was Tommy .
Hell , we buried him on Monday , and look what they did to him .
He 's only three feet long ! He must still weigh 200 pounds .
What 's all this yellow shit coming out of his head ?
Careful . Get him in there .
- Better padlock it . - Yeah .
This guy 's not gonna leak all over my ice cream , is he ?
We 'll see you back at the house .
Right .
You boys back yet ?
Jesus Christ , Myrtle . You almost gave me a coronary .
But I just can 't figure out why .
Why they 're taking these bodies and crushing them down to half size .
Crushing ' em .
What about Mom and Dad ?
They 're up there too .
Hey , just forget about that .
Okay .
I see it . I see it all now .
What we gotta do is we gotta snag that tall dude ,
and stomp the shit out of him .
And we 'll find out what the hell is going on up there .
Yeah . We 'll lay that sucker out flat and drive a stake through his goddamn heart !
You gotta be shittin ' me , man . That mother 's strong .
Hey , hold on . First thing is , I want Mike out of here .
JODY : Reg , you take him over to Sally 's , the antique store .
He 'll be safe there . Then hustle on back .
And , Mike , no arguments .
SALLY : Jody sure sounded strange on the phone .
I hope he 's feeling okay .
Sally , did you see these new settings ?
Oh , these are nice .
You know , I think I 'm gonna lock up .
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
SALLY : Michael , when you get sleepy , I 've got a bed made up for you in back .
[ TICKING CONTINUES ]
- You have to take me home . - But why ?
No questions . You must take me home .
[ PLAYING " THREE BLIND MICE " ]
[ THUMPING NOISE ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ RUSTLING NOISE ]
[ HOWLING ]
[ GROWLING ]
Oh , my God . Pull over .
MICHAEL : Stay in the car and don 't get out . I 'll be right back .
SALLY : Michael , wait a minute .
SALLY : Is that Reggie 's truck ?
Let 's get out of here , quick !
- Michael , what is going on ? - Just get me home .
[ RATTLING ]
- What the hell is that ? - [ RATTLING CONTINUES ]
- [ RATTLING ] - Oh , shit !
Get out of here .
Don 't open it !
- No ! - [ SCREAMS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ DOOR SLAMS SHUT ]
Oh , God .
It got Sally and Suzy .
What ?
Up at Morningside .
And Reggie too .
You better get on up to your room .
- I 'm goin ' with you . - Nope .
I 'm not lettin ' you go by yourself .
Let me go , goddamn it !
Son of a bitch ! You 're not lettin ' me go , are ya ?
You 're never coming back , you goddamn bastard !
Don 't leave me alone !
Open the damn door !
[ PANTING ]
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
I 've been waiting for you .
[ GROANS ]
[ WICKED LAUGHTER ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
He has to be in there .
[ WHIRRING NOISE ]
I 'm sorry , Daddy ...
but we had to .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ WHIRRING NOISE ]
Oh , my God !
- Jody ? - Yeah ?
I opened up his ...
Forget it .
Come on .
There 's this door down here ...
and I 'll bet there 's something behind it .
Let 's take a look then .
Well , that 's the door .
- Hey , man , I don 't know ... - Hey !
- Hi , guys . - Reg ! You ain 't dead .
No , and I ain 't three foot two yet , either .
- What 's goin ' on ? - Hey , man , I don 't know .
I 've been hidin ' in a casket , playin ' like a stiff .
But I did find the girls .
I found Sally and Sue , and a couple other girls I never even saw before .
- Were they dead ? - No .
I snuck ' em out a window , and they took off through the bushes like scared rabbits .
All right .
Well , after you , my friend .
You be my guest , man .
Jesus .
Dwarves !
God , Reggie ! Look at this .
[ WHISTLING SOUND ]
FEMALE VOICE : Don 't fear .
Wow .
- [ WHISTLING SOUND ] - [ SCREAMS ]
[ HOWLING ]
Jesus !
God ! I just grabbed him there .
[ WHISPERING ] Slaves .
- What ? - Slaves .
They 're using them for slaves .
The dwarves .
And they gotta crush ' em 'cause of the gravity ...
and the heat .
And this is the door to their planet .
- [ SNAPS FINGERS ] - Yeah .
And these guys are all ready to go .
Yeah .
- JODY : Okay , stay together . - MIKE : Wait a sec . I think I got a lighter .
JODY : Quick , light it up .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GROWLING SOUNDS ]
JODY : Over here . Follow me .
- [ FOOTSTEPS ] - [ DOOR BANGS SHUT ]
REGGIE : Jody , where are ya ?
Mike !
[ GROWLING SOUNDS ]
Ah , shit !
REGGIE : Mike !
Mike , where are ya ?
Mike !
[ POWER GENERATOR WHIRRING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
- [ GASPS ] - [ EXPLOSION ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
[ BANGING ]
- [ WIND HOWLING ] - Jody !
Jody , where are ya !
Jody ! Jody !
Jody !
[ GROANING , GASPING ]
Jody , where are ya ?
[ GASPING ]
Mike ! Mike !
Mike ! Mike , come on . We gotta find Reggie .
[ GASPING ]
[ GASPING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPING , MUMBLING ]
[ GASPING ]
Where 's Reggie ? We gotta find him .
- It 's Reggie ! - No !
- Come on ! We got to help him . - No , you can 't help him . He 's dead .
There 's a ...
there 's an old mine shaft
way down by the ... by the end of Singer 's Creek .
A thousand feet straight down .
We just gotta ... we just gotta figure a way to get him up there .
[ PANTING ]
What are we gonna do without Reggie ?
Reggie 's the last he 'll ever get ...
'cause we 're gonna run that tall bastard straight down to hell .
[ SIGHS ] Look , you go in and try to find more ammo .
I 'm gonna haul ass over there and get rid of that warning barrier
around the mine shaft and camouflage it .
Lock up the house good , man , and stay in there . I 'll be right back .
[ GROANING ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
[ WICKED LAUGHING ]
Boy !
You play a good game , boy .
But the game is finished .
Now you die .
[ PANTING ]
Don 't fear .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ VOICES HOWLING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GASPS ]
Don 't fear .
[ YELLING ]
[ THUNDERCLAPS ]
[ THUNDERCLAPS CONTINUE ]
MIKE : I hear the sounds .
I know those rocks aren 't gonna hold him .
Not for long .
Hey , you had a dream .
Just a nightmare .
What do you expect ? You 've hardly slept since the funeral last week .
I know those rocks aren 't gonna hold him .
First he took Mom and Dad ...
then he took Jody .
Now he 's after me .
Mike , that Tall Man of yours did not take Jody away .
Jody died in a car wreck .
[ WHISPERING ] Mike .
You had a bad dream .
I know you 're scared ...
but you 're not alone .
[ THUNDERCLAPS ]
I 'll take care of you .
I know I can 't ever take Jody 's place ...
but I 'm sure as hell gonna try .
It seemed so real .
You know , partner , what we need is a change of scenery .
Why don 't you and me hit the road for a couple of weeks ?
- Where 'll we go ? - [ SCOFFS ]
Well , I don 't know . I guess we can figure that one out when we get there .
Okay .
Well , get on upstairs . Get your gear together .
'Cause we leave when the sun comes up .
[ HUMMING ]
[ GASPS ]
Boy !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROWLING ]